<help size='14' color='0x000000' align='left'>

<!--                  WRITE UR HELP TAGS               -->

<step_1> Drag stem to the workarea. </step_1> 
<step_2> Drag a watch glass to the workarea. </step_2>  
<step_3> Drag a new blade to the workarea.</step_3> 
<step_4> Using blade take thin cross-sections of the stem and transfer the sections into watchglass. </step_4> 
<step_5> Drag the new slide to the workarea.</step_5> 
<step_6> Drag the safranin stain to the workarea.</step_6>
<step_7> Drag the dropper to the workarea and using it take some amount of safranin stain.</step_7>
<step_8> Add two drops of stain to the center of the slide.</step_8>
<step_9> Drag the brush to the workarea and using it select a thin section of the stem from the watchglass.</step_9>
<step_10> Transfer the section into safranin stain and leave for 2 minutes.</step_10>
<step_11> Drag a new watchglass with water to the workarea and using brush transfer the stained section into watchglass.</step_11>
<step_12> Drag a new slide to the workarea. Using brush transfer the section to the center of the slide. </step_12>
<step_13> Drag glycerine to the workarea.</step_13>
<step_14> Drag the dropper to the workarea and using it take some amount of glycerine.</step_14>
<step_15> Add two drops of glycerine over the section. </step_15>
<step_16> Drag a cover slip from the tools and keep it near the specimen.</step_16>
<step_17> Drag a needle and place it in slanting position near the glycerine solution over the section.</step_17>
<step_18> Place the cover slip above the needle, slowly remove the needle to place the cover slip over the section.</step_18>
<step_19>  Drag microscope and switch on the light. Click the diaphram to open, click the clips to open and adjust the objective lens to 10x, place the slide on the stage and close the clips to hold the slide.
1.Adjust the coarse and fine knob  to get a clear view of cross-section of stem in 10X.
2.Adjust the coarse knob to get the stage away from the objectives lens.
3.Turn the objective lens to 40X objective.
4.Adjust the coarse and fine knob to get a clear view of cross-section of stem in 40X.</step_19>

<step_20> 	</step_20>
<step_21> 	</step_21>
<step_22> 	</step_22>
<step_23> 	</step_23>
<step_24> 	</step_24>


</help>


